(Penny:)No.
(Sheldon:)You didn't really type.
(Assistant:)I didn't really have to.
(Assistant:)So how about construction?
(Sheldon:)Oh, that would be good.
Yeah, sawing, hammering,
eating out of a lunch pail...
(Sheldon:)...as my working-class fellows and I
sit perched precariously on a girder...
(Sheldon:)...high above the metropolis.
(Assistant:)No, no. This is putting up sheetrock
at a housing project in Rosemead.
(Sheldon:)-I could do that.
-Good.
(Sheldon:)-One question.
-Yes?
(Sheldon:)What's sheetrock?
(Assistant:)Moving on.
(Assistant:)How about doing deliveries
for a florist?
(Sheldon:)That seems acceptable.
(Assistant:)-Do you have your own car?
-I don't drive.
(Assistant:)Of course you don't.
(Employment Office Assistant:)Mr. Cooper,
let me just ask you a question.
(Assistant:)What was your last job?
(Sheldon:)Senior theoretical particle physicist
at CalTech, focusing on M Theory.